<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Keyvan Majd]]></title><description><![CDATA[Keyvan Majd]]></description><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/</link><item><title><![CDATA[Safe Robot Learning in Assistive Devices through Neural Network Repair]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post1/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post1/</guid><description><![CDATA[This project presents NNRepLayer: the first repair technique applied to a real physical system.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Risk-bounded Motion Planning and Control in Confined Dynamic Environment]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post2/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post2/</guid><description><![CDATA[This project addresses the "Freezing Robot" problem in dynamic confined environments. We introduced a method to bound the probability of collision to a given value in finite-time.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joint Communication and Motion Planning for Cobots]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post3/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post3/</guid><description><![CDATA[This project unifies communication and motion planning to enrich human-robot interaction, to prevent potential deadlocks and freezing situations, and to maintain the planning efficiency in terms of raveled distances.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kinematic-based Trajectory Planning Framework for Autonomous Ground Vehicles]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post4/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post4/</guid><description><![CDATA[This project presents an optimization framework for the trajectory planning problem of autonomous vehicles for a bounded time horizon.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Safety-aware Neural Network Repair for Robotic Systems with Predictive Models]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post5/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post5/</guid><description><![CDATA[This project presents a two-step supervised learning approach for safety-aware robot learning, using predictive models to enforce explicit and implicit contraints on the policy.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Safety-aware Expansion for Neural Network Repair]]></title><link>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post6/</link><guid>https://mfarazi1991.github.io/blog/post6/</guid><description><![CDATA[Inspired by the popular cascade-correlation algorithm, this project introduces a safety-aware growing neural network method aimed at expanding neural networks with new hidden units dedicated exclusively to responding to faulty samples.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>